I did some research last night.
This place is huge.
Finding Golda won't be easy.
I told them where you are.
I told them
that you're in Amoroso.
I'm really sorry, Golda.
Can we still find her here?
Do you know Golda Briones?
That sounds like Golda.
Golda!
Golda? Why are you touching me?
Do you know that this is
dressing room?
Joey, Golda is leaving.
Come here, now!
Hey, step aside!
Someone crazy blocked the way,
Ma'am.
Our revenue is going down.
When was the last time
you talked to Braganza?
Our clients are with him.
Golda.
Godfather!
I'm 99 percent sulre
I can fast-track your deal
with Braganza.
If you fix that,
I'll double your cut.
As for me, I won't leave Amoroso
until I find that Golda.
That's the only thing
that can free Father.
My boss wants to help.
She said her husband
has connections.
She said she can ask him
to look into your case.
Please tell her, thank you.
No one from the people I have
asked has recognized her yet.
That's Golda's driver.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Yvette, I'm not dating anyone,
but I'm helping someone
with a case.
Yvette, we always clash.
Usually, that's how it starts,
until you see the best
in each other.
I'm sure he can point out
where they are, Golda.
Are they going to the carnival?
Come on, let's follow them.
Watch alnd learn.
- Lllook here.
- Okay, go.
No, keep it steady.
Wait, wait, I got this.
Don't teach me.
I can do it.
Did you see that?
Saw that?
It's your luck.
- You should try that.
- One more thing, hurry up.
Steady...
Yes.
What you're teaching doesn't
make any sense.
Did you see that?
Nice.
- That's great.
- How? How?
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Jin Ho...
Are you okay?
That's nothing.
Yeah, I'm okay.
- Yeah, I'm okay, no problem.
- You want medicine?
- No problem.
- You want water?
- You want to sit down?
- No, I'm okay, I'm okay.
Watch and learn.
- Let me.
- Try.
This one, try.
I'll slhow you.
It's like this.
- I'm bored.
- Just like this.
- Wait, I'll turn around.
- Watch this.
Yes.
Check, check, check, go.
Boss...
Are you from...
Are you from Amoroso too?
Yes.
What he said?
I'll ask him againl.
So, do you work here?
Is that right?
Yes.
He said he's working here
in Amoroso.
How are you?
My friend, Korean.
You know, he's pretty slow.
Right?
-You don't know anything, right?
-Right, right.
So, where are you assigned here?
Do you think I didn't notice
you?
Boss...
No.
You've been following me
for a while.
Do you want me to kill you two
down here?
Boss, put that down.
You might pull the trigger.
I'll really pull the trigger
if you don't talk.
Boss...
Why are you following me?
Sir, put that down!
Joey, I told you not
to follow, didn't I?
I'm sorry. They're my friends.
I'm the one who ordered them
to follow you.
Why?
This. Here. Is this yours?
It was left at the eatery
earlier.
That's my girlfriend's.
Give me that.
Don't follow me.
Are you okay?
Yeah, are you okay?
Did you actually find
the necklace earlier?
No, it's fake.
I won that in the ball-throwing
game.
Turns out Mr. Driver is a liar!
I mean, so...
Do we just let him go?
I need to keep a distance.l
If we're too close,
they will get suspicious again.
But this is it.
He's really going to take us
to Golda.
A motel?
The driver is something else.
They might be staying there
overnight.
Well, let's see,
maybe they'll be fast.
Maybe they just dropped
by somewhere.
In a motel?
Will they just drop by
at a motel?
Well, with the driver's looks,
it's not just a quickie!l
He'll make the most of those
3 hours!
Three!
Three hours?
- That's it?
- Yeah, or maybe more!
Well, I'm an expert, okay,
with this stuff.
Usually, it can go on
for three hours, six hours,
or twelve hours.
You'll never know. It depends.
If they really miss each other,
they'll go on forever.
You know, watch your mouth.
You think you know a lot.
Stop there! Your mouth!
What? Are we going to follow
or not?
Okay, guys.
I'll stay here,
and you guys go home.
I will keep watch
and give you updates.
Are you sure?
Yes.
You go home.
You can go.
Let's go.
Be safe.
Two hours.
Not bad, Mister.
I thought you were sleeping.
How can I sleep?
Jin Ho hasn't come home yet.
Wow! Boyfriend? Your boyfriend?
You're really crazy, aren't you?
Of course, I'll worry.
We left him there.
But he said we should go home,
right?
He can handle that.
I'll go back to him.
What? Wait, wait.
Where are you...
where are you going?
It's late already.
What are you doing? Sit there.
Come here.
Sit there. Here. Sit.
Be careful.
Why are you so concerned
about Jin Ho?
I'm your best friend, right?
What's the connection?
The connection is huge!
You should only talk to me,
you should only ask me for help.
You should only ask me.
You should only worry about me.
Oh my, clingy.
Clingy? Well, fine
if I'm clingy.
What can I do? I love you!
How long will we turn
a blind eye, Ka-Tirada?
To checkpoints used
for extortion,
or to police officers
who accept bribes?
Ka-Tiradas, these are not
solated cases.
This is the system.
And to those who do this,
I promise you that we will not
stop until you are imprisoned
or drown in your own shadow.
And before we go straight to the
other exposes, Ka-Tiradas.
This segment is brought
to you by Pulso energy drink.
For those who are angry, awake,
and won't sleep in the fight.
And cue commercial...
Andrew, my friend at the
transportation office,
has replied about the plate
number you're checking.
Let me see.
Who is this registered to?
It's Vicente Alcala's.
What did you say?
What?
- You said...
- What?
You love me. What's that?
Love?
Who? You?
You just said it.
No.
I mean...
Of course, you're my friend.
You're my best friend, right?
So love.
- I'm your best friend, right?
- Yes.
You love me?
Yes...
So, there you go.
You know, you're a mess.
Give it a rest. Go to sleep,
okay?
I'll take care of Jin Ho.
Go ahead and rest.
Yeah, maybe I'm a bit tired.
We've been looking for Golda
all day.
That's why you really need
to rest, okay?
Get some rest.
- I'm going up.
- Okay.
- Good night.
What are you saying?
This is where you're hiding,
Golda.
Toto!
Help us here.
Okay, thank you.
I'll take care of this, Elai.
Andrew, tell me the truth.
Are you working on an expose
that we don't know about?
No, why?
So, you don't know him?
Not yet, why?
I'm just getlting to know him.
Wait...
Why?
Well, you know me.
Those you asked me to look into,
I'm doing background work.
And that Vicente Alcala,
he's not just anyone.
He's the biggest supplier of
ammunition in the Philippines.
And people call him, Godfather.
Godfather?
Godfather.
Okay, bring that.
Toto, help me.
That's the M14 and AK-47.
For the millitary?
No.
The government doesn't issue
that kind of firepower.
That's for a splecial client.
So when our deal goes through,
Godfather,
will you offer that to them too?
Of course.
Exactly.
Wow...
This is where Golda is hiding?
And they're selling guns?
Yeah. And look at this part.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Your food is ready.
Serving the food for you.
And of course, the plates.
Plates.
For you.
For us.
You really did a good job.
You just didn't know
where Golda was hiding.
You even got a video like that.
That's a big deal for us.
You know, just lucky, I guess.
Just lucky, I guess.
Whalt did you say?
No.
Oh, no, no. Don't listen to him.
Since last night,
he's difficult to talk to.
I'll just talk to Andrew
about this, okay?
- Okay.
- I'll be back.
Are you mad at lme?
Me?
Mad at you? No! You're the best!
You do everything right!
Why would I be mad at you?
You're the best.
- Never.
- Are you slure?
Eat now.
In Amoroso?
You know, Golda was my informant
for five years,
but we never had an operation
there.
And I know she has no relatives
there, she has no connections.
She's not just an informant.
She's also a criminal
and a drug dealer.
Do you know who they call
the Godfather?
The Godfather?
Vincent Alcala?
My assistant told me he has
the largest supplies
of ammunition in the government.
Not just the government.
Also, rebels, private armies,
and terrorists.
Why, Andrew?
Is Golda there now?
I'm not sure,
but there'sl a possibility.
Be careful.
That's a big syndicate.
And Joey...
We know she's impulsive.
She will not give up.
You take care of her first.
Andrew, this guy won't respect
you.
So, what's the plan?
It seems like we have no choice
but to enter the villa
of that Godfather.
We can't pull this mission off
if you're acting like this.
Do you know the house
of Vicente Alcala?
The events team sent me
for the party.
I want to ask for help
from your husband.
I was just thinking,
if you could help me
with something.
Her husband is in jail.
His name is Miguel Delgado,
former Major Miguel Delgado.
You know, there are people
who feel like superheroes.
- Are you talking about me?
- Why would I talk about you?
- Are you guys fighting?
- No!
I think one more shot.
Andrew, join us!
- Game?
- Game.
- Truth or Dare.
- Spin.
Your turn.
- Truth or Dare.
- Truth.